

I have been working as a web designer/developer and graphic designer for over 10 years. I love clean, elegant, simple styling, and have lots of experience in the production using CSS3, HTML5, javascript, PHP, MySQL, & many more for modern websites. I love creating awesome design as per clients' need. I think of user experience when I try to craft something for my clients. Making a design awesome.

# **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

INDESIGN	••••
ILLUSTRATOR	••••
PHOTOSHOP	••••
PREMIERE	••••
FLASH	••••
DREAMWEAVER	••••
ATOM	••••

### **CODING SKILLS**

HTML	••••
PHP	••••
MYSQL	••••
JAVASCRIPT	••••
CSS	••••
AJAX	••••

#### **WEB** frameworks

WORDPRESS LARAVEL	••••	
	••••	
BOOTSTRAP	••••	

### OS

WINDOWS	••••
MAC OS	••••

# **LOUIE CARMONA**

+97150 604 6545 / louie@carmona.design

PORTFOLIO www.carmona.design

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2010 to PRESENT

AMED ADVERTISING Aspect Tower, Business Bay, Dubai UAE Web & Magazine Creative Designer

Developed the magazine template from cover to cover for the company.

Designs the corresponding website of the magazines.

Designs, maintains and updates websites on regular basis.

Designs and layout magazine pages and covers for the company.

Designs and develops logos, create and applies to all the collaterals needed.

Understanding of branding & oversee projects.

Prepares work to be accomplished by gathering information and materials.

Ensure delivery of high standard of work on time within deadline.

Responsible for all I.T. administration and related support needed in the company. Established the creative department of the company and hired key people for it.

2006 to 2010

◆ PROPERTY GUIDE Project Dubai, Internet City, Dubai UAE Magazine Art Director & Web Administrator

Design pages and covers for the company's magazines

Property Finders Guide Magazine

Designs marketing collaterals for the company and its clients.

Designs and develops logos, with application to all collaterals required.

Designs, develops, maintains and updates the company's websites.

Obtains approval of concept by submitting rough layout for approval.

Responsible for all I.T. administration and related support needed in the company.

2002 to 2006

▶ **DOTCOM SYSTEMS** Sheikh Zayed Road, Dubai UAE Graphic Designer & Web Designer

Designs marketing collaterals for the company and its clients.

Designs and develops logos, with application to all collaterals required.

Contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed

Prepares final layout by marking and pasting up finished copy and art.

Maintains and updates websites.

### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS











# **EDUCATION**

2000 to 2002

STI COLLEGE

Website Design & Development

1995 to 2000

LYCEUM OF BATANGAS
BS in Computer Science

1991 to 1995

**STA THERESA COLLEGE**Secondary Education

# **PROFILE**

Religion:

Nationality: Filipino

Mobile: +91750 604 6545 E-mail: louie@carmona.design

Roman Catholic

Marital Status: Married Language: English

Gender: Male

With a valid U.A.E driving license